Friends, the quarterly results of Indian Hotel Company are
out. Net profit has jumped to Rs
582 crore. Revenue has increased from Rs 29 crore. You
can see this. This is an update. This is the quarterly
result. So, here you
can check the complete result, like how much growth has happened,
how much was there last year.
You can check all these details here.
Apart from this, the future said the company is well poised
to reach 700 hotels by 2030. By 2030, there can be 700 hotels.
This is basically said. You can see this. Apart from this,
as I have shared the result of Wipo
with you in the afternoon, the
quarterly result of SBI Life's Tech Marka is also out. You can see this.
In the quarterly result of Tech Marka, the
net profit has jumped to Rs 92 crore. Year-on-year
profit has reached Rs 983 crore.
You can see the revenue of Rs 1.4 crore. This is the
complete quarterly result. You can check it.
If you have any doubt in this, you
can message in the comment section or you
can check it completely
in this.  Apart from this, the quarterly results of ICICI Lord
ICICI Lord General Insurance have also been
out, the net
profit rise has jumped from 68 to
700 724 crores, you can see this, this is the
quarterly result, check it,
if you have any doubt in it then you
can message in the comment section,
apart from this there is more news which I would like to share with you one by one,
apart from this the selling
pressure from A continued today also, A
sold shares worth 33180 crores today and D
countered by purchasing shares worth 2572 8 crores,
friends, Kotak Securities, sorry Kotak
's brokerage company has
given a sell call on the trend, the target price has been cut
from 14, a target of about 5850 has been given, you
can see this, Kotak Enala Top 10 Series by tone
count
of Jude Highlight, so their target price has been
basically reduced, you can see this
of the trade, I am sharing this with you,
you can see it completely, the target price which
they have given is given below 14, they have
given about 5850, you can see it
Apart from this, as you can see,
sorry
[music]
like GH CL RCF fertilizer
and chemical other chemical stocks, Rally % A
soda S price rise, you can see this, soda
S price rise globally leading sharp Rally
domestic chemical and fertilizer stocks, so
somewhere or the other it had an impact, you can see in these three shares Gujarat
Heavy Chemical GSFC and Laksh Chemical,
this is the complete update, you
can check it, if you have any
doubt, you can message in the comment section,
friends, this is an update related to the industry, the
broker has set its target price, you
can see it and as you
can check on the target price,
like Nma Research has maintained buy call and has
given a target of 1673, you can see this, this
is the complete update, if you have any doubt in this, you
can message in the comment,
apart from this, as you can see,
Sela has covered Indo TVS today, has
given an upside target of around 62, you can see this,
somewhere or the other its impact was seen in the share
Even in the negative market, the share was
positive today, so they have
given a target of Rs 575 for the share, you can see this, this is an
update, you
can check it, if you like the video then
like, share and subscribe.